chinesezodiachoroscope.com 2017-12-29

# None

****

Welcome to Chinese Horoscope, a personal online service operated by Pluckysoft Inc. 

Your privacy is important to us and, as described in this Privacy Policy, we have designed the Service to protect information about you from unauthorized disclosure to others. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and, in certain circumstances, share your personally identifying information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us.

By using the Service, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy, as such policy may be amended from time to time. We may update the Privacy Policy and if we do, we will post a notice that changes have been made on this application. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy.

**What We Collect**

When you add the application it asks you to enter your birth date. This is required for the application to calculate your Chinese Zodiac sign as well as Western sign which is displayed on various pages. We store this information along with your Facebook user id number in order to facilitate the ability to look up friends' signs correctly and accurately. This information is also used to provide you with the correct horoscopes in regards to your sign as well as various other features related to your sign.

We maintain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Pluckysoft Inc on the Chinese Horoscope application.

By using the service, you consent to our retaining the information to display on the application as well as our website at ChineseHoroscope.org.

**Children Under The Age Of 13**

Chinese Horoscope does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Chinese Horoscope or send any information about yourself to us. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Chinese Horoscope. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us.

**Children Between The Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

**How We Use Your Information**

We do not sell or rent your "Personally Identifiable Information" to any third party. We may, however, use certain information about you that is not personally identifiable.

We use public information collected to determine the kinds of content that you would like to view and to assist any advertisers in targeting their advertising.

We also use your name, email address and other information on our system to notify you of new product releases, service notifications, solicit your feedback and input, and provide you with free monthly horoscopes and other horoscope related information. Those emails will contain links for preference management and where appropriate, unsubscribe links should you decide you do not want to receive further emails.

You understand and agree that we may access, preserve, and disclose any information we may have about you and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect our rights and property, or that of our affiliates or the public.

Chinese Horoscope may maintain copies of your Content indefinitely, or delete certain Content in whole or in part if Chinese Horoscope determines, in its sole discretion that it is in the best interest of the application.

**Controlling Your Personal Information**

Be advised that if you send messages or post material containing personal information, that information may be collected and used by others.

You can terminate your account at any time by removing the application. Chinese Horoscope, however, may (but is not obligated to) keep information about you that is on its system following your termination. Please contact Chinese Horoscope to terminate your account or for any other questions about your personal information.

**Cookies**

The Service sends "cookies" to your computer when you access the ChineseHoroscope.org site and the Service uses such cookies as described in here. The Service uses cookies to improve the quality of our service, make recommendations, and make the Service easier to use for our users. A cookie is a small text file recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user and contains certain information about your particular login session and/or your use of the Service.

**Use of Information**

Chinese Horoscope may contain links to other web sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information. It is up to you to review those policies yourself. 

**Third-Party Advertising Companies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site. These are mainly from Google Adsense but may contain links from other advertisers. Our advertisers may use cookies or other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on our site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your computer. Similarly, third-party advertising companies may provide us with pixel tags (also called "clear gifs" or "beacons") to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the site on which the beacon is located, and to learn which banner ads bring users to a given site. 

Chinese Horoscope does not provide any Personally Identifiable Information to third-party advertising companies.

**Security**

Chinese Horoscope takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of the application, please contact us.

**Additional Questions**

Feel free to contact us by sending an email to plucky@pluckysoft.com, any time, if you have further questions about Chinese Horoscope or this Privacy Policy.
